<history><t>1.2.5 Small Bug Fix and Features Sprint<d>11-10-2012</d></t><i>Switched .Net 4.0 with .Net 4.5 allowing more than 2GB memory usage for one vApus instance.</i><i>A new solution can now be created from a template.</i><i>Simplified the vApus updater, all settings are done in the settings panel, the updater window is now just a checksum list.</i><i>Simplified the connection proxies editor.</i><i>Fixed the custom list generator.</i><i>Minor issues with the wizard, run sync and monitor report tabs fixed.</i><i>Parameters can be used in a test with action and log entry distribution now.</i><i>Monitors can start before and end after a test.</i><i>And a whole bunch of smaller issues...</i><t>1.2.0 Released!<d>01-10-2012</d></t><i>User friendly distributed testing, complete with wizard.</i><t>Properties (1.1.1)<d>11-05-2012</d></t><i>Properties of an item (stresstest for instance) default to the first available item in the solution (if applicable).</i><i>Removed some property controls (like for Label) from the property panels.</i><t>Monitoring (1.1.0)<d>02-05-2012</d></t><i>Stable monitoring added.</i><t>Options (1.0.9)<d>25-04-2012</d></t>vApus checks if the Windows firewall and/or the Windows Auto Update is enabled, you can and should disable them from within vApus.<t>Update Notifier (1.0.9)<d>25-04-2012</d></t><i>Shows changelog when vApus detects an update.</i><t>HotFix Monitor View (1.0.8)<d>24-04-2012</d></t><i>It was impossible to monitor while stresstesting because the counters were not filled in correctly.</i><t>Connection View (1.0.7)<d>24-04-2012</d></t><i>The connection route can be traced from this view.</i><t>Connection Proxy Code View (1.0.7)<d>23-04-2012</d></t><i>Updates the panel while scrolling now.</i><t>Bug reporting (1.0.6)<d>18-04-2012</d></t><i>It is now possible to report bugs from the application log panel in vApus to Sizing Servers.</i><t>Custom List Parameters (1.0.5)<d>17-04-2012</d></t><i>Removed label control from generate from type dialog.</i><i>Can now be generated from custom random parameter.</i><t>Custom Random Parameter (1.0.5)<d>16-04-2012</d></t><i>Added line numbers</i><i>Test code button now instead of try compile.</i><t>Numeric Parameters (1.0.5)<d>13-04-2012</d></t><i>Decimal separator can be set here.</i><t>Flat style controls (1.0.5)<d>13-04-2012</d></t><i>For parameters and connection proxy GUI.</i><t>Stopping a scheduled test (1.0.4)<d>13-04-2012</d></t><i>A stresstest could not be stopped before the test was actually started (while the schedule timer was running).</i><t>Fixed Connection Proxy Code Scrolling (1.0.3)<d>12-04-2012</d></t><i>When clicking around the view was very prone to scroll to the wrong place.</i><t>HotFix Connection Proxy Code (1.0.2)<d>10-04-2012</d></t><i>Connections could not be tested from here anymore.</i><t>HotFix Parameters (1.0.1)<d>28-03-2012</d></t><i>Numeric parameters did not always respect its given boundaries.</i><t>First Master Build (1.0.0 DUBLIN)<d>14-03-2012</d></t><i>Codename DUBLIN</i></history>