<history><t>1.10.0 RC 2<d>27-02-2015</d></t><i>An overview export of results to Excel is added: stress test concurrency results next to monitor results in the same sheet for multiple results dbs.</i><i>IPMI monitor fixed for lanplus.</i><i>Fixed old bug that slave GUI was not rendered correctly.</i><i>Fixed progress bars for tile stresstests: realistic now.</i><i>Fixed heavy eventing and wrong rendering event progress bars.</i><i>Bugs can be reported to Redmine from within vApus again.</i><i>Minor bug fixes.</i><t>1.10.0 RC<d>14-01-2015</d></t><i>Stress test progress logs are now saved to the results database.</i><i>Replaced the welcome view with a first run view.</i><i>Minor bug fixes.</i><i>Export to Excel augmentations:</i><i>Auto-export possible.</i><i>Gauss chart per concurrency for response times.</i><i>Top 5 average and 99th percentile of the response times.</i><t>1.9.0<d>18-11-2014</d></t><i>Bug fixing of the monitors and some small GUI and usability fixes.</i><i>Added some extra metrics to stress test results.</i><t>1.9.0 RC<d>02-10-2014</d></t><i>New monitor framework! This means that you must check your vass files and use the new monitor agents. A new personal.xlsm must be used as well.</i><i>There is a button in the monitor panel to default to pre-defined counters to monitor.</i><t>1.8.7<d>25-09-2014</d></t><i>HotFixed hanging GUI because of wrong parameters event initialisations.</i><t>1.8.7 RC<d>08-09-2014</d></t><i>Fixes focus issues and wrongly calculated average user action results in the detailed results viewer.</i><i>A number of small bug fixes.</i><t>1.8.5<d>15-05-2014</d></t><i>Various 1.8.0 bug fixes, mostly things that worked in 1.7.0 but not in 1.8.0 anymore.</i><t>1.8.0 Speeding things up part two<d>13-01-2014</d></t><i>Loading a vass and starting a distributed test is more streamlined.</i><i>Added a JSON monitor for an internal HotBox project.</i><i>Added linked parameters.</i><t>1.7.0 Speeding things up and multiple logs<d>20-12-2013</d></t><i>Numerous changes where made to speed up single and distributed test initialisation times.</i><i>Sped up fetching detailed results through the means of caching.</i><i>Added categories in the Detailed Results Export To Excel dialog.</i><i>Multiple selected results can now be deleted in the Detailed Results Viewer.</i><i>Multiple logs plus usage distribution can be added to a test, allowing more heterogeneous usage patterns for a user.</i><i>Moved the Errors column more forward in the fast and detailed results.</i><i>If calculating the fast results takes longer than 3 seconds, the user gets a warning and a more simplified result set is presented. This is to make sure that the GUI thread does not become a bottleneck when testing using a large log.</i><i>A number of bug fixes including linked user actions not working properly in a distributed test.</i><i>Adopted the .Net Framework 4.5.1.</i><t>1.6.5 Many-to-one plus run sync<d>08-10-2013</d></t><i>Yes, you can!</i><i>Vastly improved test init times, tested using a 100k log.</i><i>Added a Runs over Time chart to the detailed results Excel export.</i><i>The description table in a results db has a primary key now, to be able to edit the description afterwards.</i><i>Fixed smart update</i><t>1.6.0 Many-to-one Distributed Testing<d>29-08-2013</d></t><i>A stresstest can be assigned to multiple slaves in a distributed test now. The workload of such a test will be divided over those slaves, this to be able to use multiple clients for a very heavy workload. Please note that this WON'T work in combination with run sync! That will be supported in the next version of vApus.</i><i>Added a maximum rerun counter for break on last run sync, located right next the run sync combo box.</i><i>Due to a new eventing approach vApus feels much smoother.</i><i>Various small features and bug fixes.</i><i>All code is fully re-factored and commented to make it easier and faster to fix bugs and add features.</i><t>1.5.7.5<d>18-06-2013</d></t><i>Monitor before and after data is now in the fast and the detailed results.</i><i>Distributed testing GUI is a lot faster now.</i><i>A reopen solution item is added in the File menu.</i><i>It is possible to delete multiple results databases at once in the stand-alone detailed results viewer.</i><i>A number of minor issues are fixed.</i><t>1.5.7.1<d>06-06-2013</d></t><i>Fixed testing with user action distribution.</i><t>1.5.7<d>05-06-2013</d></t><i>Renamed Cummulative to Cumulative and Overview in the Detailed Results and the Excel export.</i><i>Added an Errors column in Overview.</i><i>Replaced line breaks with a dot for readability in the User Action Composition.</i><i>The style is fixed in the text import of the log editor</i><i>Fixed the style in the User Action editor view.</i><i>Log entries can contain line breaks now.</i><i>Removing multiple user actions is way faster now.</i><i>In some cases moving linked users did not work.</i><i>The Windows Firewall can be disabled once again from within vApus.</i><i>Another .vass file can be opened if one is already opened without vApus stalling.</i><t>1.5.5.1<d>17-5-2013</d></t><i>Tests with more than two user actions in a link did not work.</i><t>1.5.5<d>15-05-2013</d></t><i>Options dialog has been tweaked and has no more UI artefacts.</i><i>Results in a tile stresstest view update now without clearing the test progress label.</i><i>The overview node is now selected when starting a distributed test, so you can directly see what vApus is doing.</i><i>A "Select Next Available Slave" button is added to the tile stresstest view.</i><i>Deleting a results database in the detailed results app does not longer make it crash.</i><i>Exporting detailed results to an Excel file does now generate larger charts, if you copy those to a Word document the whole page is used.</i><i>When having a large number of concurrencies the stresstest wouldn't start.</i><t>1.5.0<d>08-05-2013</d></t><i>A brand new log editor!</i><i>Please open your old logs with it and save, otherwise stresstesting won't work!</i><i>Revert to imported only works for new logs.</i><t>1.4.2<d>02-05-2013</d></t><i>Added retry connect logic for distributed tests.</i><t>1.4.1<d>16-04-2013</d></t><i>Hotfix for when saving monitor results with duplicate column names.</i><t>1.4.0<d>02-04-2013</d></t><i>vApus can now communicate with slave instances over IPv6, connecting from a master to a slave is best done using the hostname, this is now better supported.</i><i>Saving charts from the detailed results is now expanded with other data and renamed to Export to Excel.</i><i>Monitors did sometimes crashed when used together with a stresstest, configuring monitors was also slow.</i><i>The distributed test wizard was slow and did sometimes show passwords.</i><t>1.4.0<d>02-04-2013</d></t><i>vApus can now communicate with slave instances over IPv6, connecting from a master to a slave is best done using the hostname, this is now better supported.</i><i>Saving charts from the detailed results is now expanded with other data and renamed to Export to Excel.</i><i>Monitors did sometimes crashed when used together with a stresstest, configuring monitors was also slow.</i><i>The distributed test wizard was slow and did sometimes show passwords.</i><t>1.3.2<d>19-03-2013</d></t><i>Chart output to Excel is available in the detailed results viewer</i><i>Slaves can be updated automatically when starting a distributed test, this is an option in the Update Notifier options</i><i>Send mail at events is now available for distributed tests</i><i>Detailed results are now correct when using Distribute Fast or Full in a stresstest</i><i>Fixed localization for monitor and Excel output</i><i>Numerous other smaller bug fixes</i><t>1.3.1<d>26-02-2013</d></t><i>Fixed results for run synchronization</i><i>Added the old report viewer for backwards compatibility</i><i>ISO 8601 is used for date and time formatting</i><t>1.3.0<d>13-02-2013</d></t><i>Distributed test results can be written to a MySQL database</i><i>vApus can (only) store results to MySQL 5.6 GA now</i><i>A stand-alone detailed results viewer is added</i><i>Various bug fixes regarding distributed testing</i><t>1.2.9<d>21-01-2013</d></t><i>Switched to MySQL (5.6.7.2-rc) for result saving, to be included in the installer in 1.3.0</i><i>Switched to dynamic result views for single and distributed tests</i><i>Fixed window freeze when changing values</i><i>Various small bug fixes</i><t>1.2.5.2 HotFix<d>09-11-2012</d></t><i>Connection and log numbering became incorrect when starting a distributed test</i><t>1.2.5.1 HotFix<d>09-11-2012</d></t><i>User Action and Log Entry Distribution broke distributed tests.</i><t>1.2.5 Small Bug Fix and Features Sprint<d>11-10-2012</d></t><i>Switched .Net 4.0 with .Net 4.5 allowing more than 2GB memory usage for one vApus instance.</i><i>A new solution can now be created from a template.</i><i>Simplified the vApus updater, all settings are done in the settings panel, the updater window is now just a checksum list.</i><i>Simplified the connection proxies editor.</i><i>Fixed the custom list generator.</i><i>Minor issues with the wizard, run sync and monitor report tabs fixed.</i><i>Parameters can be used in a test with action and log entry distribution now.</i><i>Monitors can start before and end after a test.</i><i>And a whole bunch of smaller issues...</i><t>1.2.0 Released!<d>01-10-2012</d></t><i>User friendly distributed testing, complete with wizard.</i><t>Properties (1.1.1)<d>11-05-2012</d></t><i>Properties of an item (stresstest for instance) default to the first available item in the solution (if applicable).</i><i>Removed some property controls (like for Label) from the property panels.</i><t>Monitoring (1.1.0)<d>02-05-2012</d></t><i>Stable monitoring added.</i><t>Options (1.0.9)<d>25-04-2012</d></t>vApus checks if the Windows firewall and/or the Windows Auto Update is enabled, you can and should disable them from within vApus.<t>Update Notifier (1.0.9)<d>25-04-2012</d></t><i>Shows changelog when vApus detects an update.</i><t>HotFix Monitor View (1.0.8)<d>24-04-2012</d></t><i>It was impossible to monitor while stresstesting because the counters were not filled in correctly.</i><t>Connection View (1.0.7)<d>24-04-2012</d></t><i>The connection route can be traced from this view.</i><t>Connection Proxy Code View (1.0.7)<d>23-04-2012</d></t><i>Updates the panel while scrolling now.</i><t>Bug reporting (1.0.6)<d>18-04-2012</d></t><i>It is now possible to report bugs from the application log panel in vApus to Sizing Servers.</i><t>Custom List Parameters (1.0.5)<d>17-04-2012</d></t><i>Removed label control from generate from type dialog.</i><i>Can now be generated from custom random parameter.</i><t>Custom Random Parameter (1.0.5)<d>16-04-2012</d></t><i>Added line numbers</i><i>Test code button now instead of try compile.</i><t>Numeric Parameters (1.0.5)<d>13-04-2012</d></t><i>Decimal separator can be set here.</i><t>Flat style controls (1.0.5)<d>13-04-2012</d></t><i>For parameters and connection proxy GUI.</i><t>Stopping a scheduled test (1.0.4)<d>13-04-2012</d></t><i>A stresstest could not be stopped before the test was actually started (while the schedule timer was running).</i><t>Fixed Connection Proxy Code Scrolling (1.0.3)<d>12-04-2012</d></t><i>When clicking around the view was very prone to scroll to the wrong place.</i><t>HotFix Connection Proxy Code (1.0.2)<d>10-04-2012</d></t><i>Connections could not be tested from here anymore.</i><t>HotFix Parameters (1.0.1)<d>28-03-2012</d></t><i>Numeric parameters did not always respect its given boundaries.</i><t>First Master Build (1.0.0 DUBLIN)<d>14-03-2012</d></t><i>Codename DUBLIN</i></history>